Contact

+600132398323 (Mobile) nwy140@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/ng-weiyuen-9a0a72145 (LinkedIn) gamejolt.com/games/ spacerocketboost/360408 (Portfolio) play.google.com/store/apps/details (Portfolio) nwy140.github.io/nwyPortfolio/ (Portfolio)

Top Skills

C++

C#

Java

Certifications

The Complete Unity Indie Game Developer Course Certificate of Completion

The Unreal Engine Developer
Course - Learn C++ & Make Games
Course Certificate of Completion

The Java Programming Language Course 2017 Certificate of Completion

IGCSE

Game Asset Crash Course - 3D Modeling in Blender and 3D-Coat Certificate of Completion

Honors-Awards

LEVEL UP @ Schools Game Awards Under 18 GameJam Finalist

Ng Wei Yuen

Hobbyist Game Developer | Former Game Programmer Intern at SodaPunkGames

Selangor

Summary

Hobbyist Game Developer and App Developer.

1.5 Year of Experience in Game Development.

Worked on a new game title and a few other small personal game projects.

Started working on game development ever since I finished high school.

Always seeking to learn and utilize new technology such as Flutter, React Native, Virtual Reality and the Unreal Engine

University of Utah Freshman with some experiences and connections to the Malaysian Game Industry.

The real reason why I chose to go the University of Utah is because I wanted to enter/network with the American Game Industry.

Experience

Silent Wolf Studios Indie Game Developer June 2017 - Present

Kuala Lumpur, Malaysia

SilentWolfStudios is a pen name that I use for any personal game projects that I've worked on.

My personal game project SpaceRocketBoost is selected as a top finalist for the LEVEL UP @ Schools Game Awards Under 18 GameJam.

Please checkout my game development portfolio on GameJolt and Playstore PC: https://gamejolt.com/games/spacerocketboost/360408 (GameJolt)
Android: http://tosto.re/spacerocketboost (Google PlayStore)

Sodapunk Games Plt Game Programmer Intern June 2018 - July 2018 (2 months) Malaysia

Sodapunk Games Plt is a startup that develops cool innovative games.

Unreal Engine Gameplay Programmer.

Worked on the Special Weapons of TR3K and optimized the weapon mechanics for multiplayer

(i.e debugging the network replication between server and clients or on a dedicated server, and making sure all the projectiles get fired on all clients and the server).

Teaser Trailer: https://www.facebook.com/SodaPunkGames/videos/1059708977524605

Super Sushi Sdn Bhd Waiter September 2017 - October 2017 (2 months) 1 Utama

Worked as a waiter in a local shopping mall.

ABNG

Clerk

August 2017 - September 2017 (2 months)

Kuala Lumpur, Malaysia

During this time, I started learning app development on my own. And began to work on some hobbyist projects, in which a few of them have been released to the google play app store.

As of 2018, those apps are currently generating a passive income of at least \$4 USD per month.

You can find some of the source code of my personal projects in my git repositories online

Repositories.

Github: https://github.com/nwy140

GitLab: https://gitlab.com/users/nwy140/projects

Education

University of Utah

Computer Science In Games with EAE Emphasis, Computer

Science · (2019 - 2023)

Sunway University

Monash University Foundation Year · (2018 - 2018)

Sri KDU International School Cambridge IGCSE · (2012 - 2017)

<u>Letter of Recommendation for Ng Wei Yuen</u>

To whomever it may concern,

This letter is to address and support Mr Ng Wei Yuen for his scholarship application. Ng Wei Yuen used to be an intern for about 2 months in my previous startup company, Sodapunk Games in Malaysia. He had proved himself that he possessed comparatively strong grasp of knowledge among the peers of his age on utilizing game engines such as Unity and Unreal in developing mobile games and apps.

During his duration of working as an intern with me, he possessed excellent problem solving and capable of deliver his task in a timely manner. He is also a very resourceful person that will do research proactively when facing certain problems while developing our games. Aside from that, he is capable of developing quick and interesting game mechanic prototypes while working with me.

As for challenges, he had some difficulty when trying to convey information to past colleagues but this shortcomings is easily mitigated by his positive and highly proactive attitude in asking relevant questions when he faced difficulties.

Overall, he possessed great academic qualities for being a quick learner, good problem solver and already had more knowledge of the field he is pursuing (IT, mobile apps development, games development) than most peers at his age just by self learning. Hence, I strongly recommended him to be qualified for the scholarship he is applying for.

Shall there be any questions, below are my contact information:

Email: laizr03@gmail.com

Linkedin: https://www.linkedin.com/in/laizeren94/

Best Regards, Lai Ze Ren



Malaysia Digital Economy Corporation Sdn Bhd (289346-D) 2360 Persiaran APEC, 63000 Cyberjaya, Selangor Darul Ehsan Malaysia

T+603 8315 3000 F+603 8315 3115

Date: 10th December 2018

To whom it may concern,

It's my absolute pleasure to recommend Ng Wei Yuen (NRIC Number: 010115101653) with the address of No. 11, Jalan BU4/7, Bandar Utama, 47800 Petaling Jaya, Selangor, Malaysia for his application as undergraduate student at your institution.

I have gotten to know Wei Yuen as he had proactively participated in LEVEL UP @ Schools Game Awards, a national game development competition organized by MDEC as part of our talent development initiatives.

Through-out the competition Wei Yuen has show dedication during the showcase at mydigitalmaker fair (https://www.mydigitalmaker.com/mydigitalmaker-fair-2018). He is smart, analytical, dependable, and incredibly hard-working. Beyond that, he is always a curious student who always ask the right questions during the event and work the hardest to improve his game through the feedback from the audience. His knowledge of game programming and his ability to proactively learn Unreal Engine and Unity on his own are among his best strength.

Beyond that he also participated in LEVEL UP KL 2018, a premier game development conference in Southeast Asia, and other activities as well such as local game developer gathering, playtest sessions and talk sessions. This truly proves his passion in the game industry.

Without a doubt, I confidently recommend Wei Yuen for his application as a undergraduate student. As a dedicated and knowledgeable aspiring game developer, I know that he will be able to improve and learn tremendously from your prestigious institution.

Please feel free to contact me at bazil.bidin@mdec.com.my or +60199682271 should you like to discuss Wei Yuen's qualifications and experience further. I'd be happy to expand on my recommendation.

Sincerely,

Bazil Akmal Bidin

Incubator Manager @ LEVEL UP Inc

bazil.bidin@mdec.com.my